Yeah,
New passage West.
And new exceptions.
So long is corrupted machines prowl the valley.
Then why don't you do something about the infestation?
We have We sealed the border.
Fine.
I'll come back once I've destroyed all the corrupted.
Ha ha ha.
Uh, if you're serious, then may you go in, like, girl and the sun guide your arrows.
Just
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
Users.
Yeah.
Okay.
Wow.
Mhm.
Yeah.
Look,
Yes.
Yeah,
yes.
I think.
Okay.
Yeah.
No.
Help yourself
a little.
Yeah.
Okay.
E o
You think?
Thank you.
Yeah,
Yeah.
Please.
Transport.
Yeah.
She
uh huh.
Yeah.
I don't know what's down here.
Leaving?
Yes.
This isn't a cave.
It's a ruin.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Woman
Okay.
Yes.
Mhm.
You
armor from the age of the old ones.
But how do I get to it?
Grab light.
I'm not getting in.
Yeah,
e Think the old ones use numbers like this to indicate time?
Me?
These devices are missing power cells.
I'll have to find power cells to get these to work.
Yeah,
this is
Yeah.
When?
Okay.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Oh,
Mhm.
Uh huh.
Try
Yeah, and
yeah,
keep quiet.
Just
Yeah,
and go.
Come on, man.
Yes.
You all right, hunter?
I'm not a hunter or brave or anything, Really.
You shouldn't even be talking to me.
Well, whoever you are, you're hurt.
What happened?
My name's Quran.
I thought I'd have a goal.
The trials of the hunting grounds over the rise told my skills.
It has.
It didn't go very well.
I was aiming for a canister on the back of a grazer and my boasting snapped and I tripped.
And things aren't exactly going your way, are they?
Is there anything I can do to help?
No, no.
I stole a bow, okay.
And got cast out.
This was before the proving.
So now I can't even fight for my tribe.
But its time of need I have to live in the wild by myself.
Which is why I wanted some training.
Honestly, I'm just glad to keep it would talk to me.
I think he might be an exile or something.
I need to get going.
Krenn.
All right, be careful, especially if you're heading north And be sure to hit the hunting grounds.
If you want to train up the keep is up there.
Underhill just to the north.
Talk to him to do a trial.
I'm sure you do better tonight.
It
Wow.
Please.
Yeah.
Sorry.
All right.
What
my friend?
Here we go again.
Okay.
E que
Yeah.
Yeah,
you know
e don't that
okay?
Have
Yeah
found advantage.
Need to piece the messages together.
A pocket She had stormed Tour Day too.
My father guest lectured here.
A 300 level military history course on the age of human air.
Power might as well as being teaching medieval siege tactics.
I was eight when he died.
Come on.
Okay,
Just
catch up.
Mhm.
We we
come on home.
Oh,
I spoke to Cran.
He told me this is a hunting grounds where you offer tests of skill.
Poor Cran.
Not the best hunter, but at least he keeps his chin up.
Mhm.
You bet the mark of a seeker.
I've heard of those, but never seen one.
You have the matriarchs leave to come and go as you like from the sacred land.
Yes, but I would have gone even without their permission.
Is that so?
That maybe you and I can speak plainly.
Truth is I've had dealings with the Kharja.
You're not supposed to be here, are you?
No, my friend and I left the sacred land on return.
We're hunters at heart left because we wanted to find new herds and new machines.
The matriarchs wouldn't approve, to say the least.
I represent an organization called the Hunter's Lodge Hunters who compete to bring down the mightiest machines in the land run by the Kharja in Meridian.
We test promising young hunters with trials in places like these each offering hunters a chance to test their skills.
You might be just the kind of person we're looking for.
What do I get for completing them?
Pride in accomplishment as well as Marx, depending on how well you fair
hunting isn't just about your bow.
It's about using everything available to you, even your surroundings.
You'll see once you start taking the trials.
Just to be clear, though, I'd appreciate it if you kept our conversation in confidence, especially when it comes to the matriarchs.
You think it'll work staying here without the matriarchs permission?
I'm not sure, but we don't believe in their rules.
There's a big world out there and ignoring it doesn't help anyone.
Testers skill with bow and arrow by shooting parts off the backs of grazers is quickly as possible.
I'll start timing when you slide down one of the ropes.
Yeah,
You know what?
Oh,
yeah.
What makes you so easier?
Mhm
people.
People
stocking up.
Yeah.
Mhm.
How do you
first time and you win a blazing sun.
You're good, even for Nora.
This trial tests your ability to use the environment to your advantage, shoot log piles to make them fall crushing machines below.
I'll start timing when you start down the room.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Thank you.
Wow.
Mm.
Yeah.
They're scary for me.
Okay.
How do you
first time and you win a blazing sun.
You're good, even for Nora.
This trial requires you to bring grazers down with blast wires, but you'll need the card, your trip, castor and ammunition to do it.
My friend here may have them for sale.
Can't wait to see what you do with that.
Use your blast wire and card your trip, Castor to bring down grazers.
I'll be timing you.
Yeah,
Yeah.
On the
Uh huh.
Mhm.
Yeah.
All right.
E
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Okay.
How would you?
First time and you win a blazing sun.
You're good, even for Nora.
You have everything you need to enter the Hunter's lodge.
Good luck in Meridian.
Of course.
You can still run Mawr trials with me.
I should go Come back when you're ready.
Yeah.
I mean,
I have three sons now.
They let me inside the hunters love.
Well, let's see how that turns out.
Yeah,
Yeah.
My feelings for the trial.
They see me?
Yeah.
Mhm.
What was coming?
Okay,
I am
No.
Okay.
Yeah.
No, I don't do it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Is it?
And
that man, he doesn't look more.
Yeah.
Excuse me
for I spoke of a bandit camp.
It's a little ruins.
That must be the place there.
Just keep an eye out around here.
Yeah.
Stay.
Logo.
Wanted to spoil the fun.
There is dangerous.
More danger than you know, Outlander.
You're trespassing on Norland.
That's forbidden.
My life is forfeit.
Yes, yes, yes!
We'll be done.
Call me.
No, Look there.
Those old rocks abandoned clan squads under them disturbed the rocks and will come wriggling out forms that they are bandits.
Why have they come here?
The Nora are in trouble.
Rumors spread like blood and no braves to guard.
The border killer is hungry for sports.
Slipping through my partner and I shadowed the scum for days.
The tracker.
But he went on ahead without we talked about this kind of the heat.
Still, I understand.
Leave it too long.
Your fingers.
It's for the boaster.
See, How about you?
And I worked together killed them all.
I don't need your help to clear up some bandits no longer.
That's except
don't worry.
If they killed you, I'll finish them off before they could make a cup of your skull.
It seems like that I don't know you and I have no reason to trust you.
Trust is a rare act to find, isn't it?
I'm just a traveler with a bow concern about the state of these lines.
And in the same part, I don't think you're just anything at all mhm.
And let me put on the edge of the way
or even better.
Of course not.
Then you have nothing to fear.
Change your mind?
No, just checking.
You weren't lining up a shot on my back.
You have my war.
Never from the back.
Yeah.
No.
Okay.
That alarm her.
Wake up the whole camp and more.
Besides.
Okay, alarms down.
Heard something.
Hi.
Are right near my damn face.
Sure
she's coming for us.
Yeah,
I'll finish you.
Oh,
get it together.
Luck.
You won't survive this.
Yeah,
Okay.
He
Yeah.
What's in your head?
They must make abandons prisoners.
What do you wanna be?
Year?
School,
right?
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
Make
all right.
Yeah.
I'm gonna get you out.
You're coming with me.
Okay.
Search is off.
Yeah.
I gotta pick it up in the move.
Can't see him.
No.
Here we are.
Yeah.
Seeker, May I speak with you?
I'm honored.
I all Mother be praised.
Are you all right?
Is there something you need?
Yes.
My friends and I watched you clear the bandits out of this camp.
We're glad
they would steal from us.
Chase us through the night laughing.
We're outcasts, not braves.
Almost defenseless.
Where did you all come from?
Some of us have wandered the sacred lands for years.
As for me, the village I grew up in was burned in the red raids.
I'm ashamed.
I wasn't there to protect them.
But I was an outcast long before the Kharja came.
How did you all come to be here together?
You wonder how we speak to each other when the law forbids it.
But what hope do we have here outside the embrace alone?
I wasn't judging you.
I wasn't outcast once.
Forgive me.
You're right to ask.
I convinced them to speak.
I told them we were only sentenced to be outcast, not to die out here.
An intelligent approach.
I was a fool.
I refused to do what I was told.
Never went hunting when I could sit under a tree.
Instead I argued with my family Every step picked fights with other braves.
One day such a fight grew fierce.
I got a lucky hit.
Unlucky one.
He went down and there was no one left to speak for me.
I deserve to be an outcast.
You seem different from the person you describe I hope to be.
We are all outcasts But we need to stay together to survive this camp we once hated could serve us well.
Now would you let us stay here even if it flies in the face of the matriarchs laws.
Of course.
By all means.
Uh huh.
I'd hoped you'd say so.
You uran inspiration.
Tow us.
Thank you.
Thank you for making this possible.
Yeah,
Yeah.
I'll admit at first I felt slighted by your selfishness.
But, you know, I'm glad I stayed to one every kill, you know, break my fingers on a narrow had distant to feel part
You're keeping score.
What's wrong with you?
I saw you through.
I didn't find your partner today.
Children.
I hardly feel surprised.
He was already getting cocky when we carved through the last time.
I thought, you know mhm en enjoy the killing as much as the check.
No great loss.
Nothing in the wilds I can't handle just me and the voice of our teeth.
You
here?
Bo has a name.
Yours doesn't You're not just a traveler.
That army was fitted for you and the way you hold your boat.
I said a concern.
I was a surgery, but I was a soldier longer than there was a war.
If you follow where the arrowhead passes between armor and skin, that's the place on.
So I make opportunities to find it That's right.
Coming.
Have you ever thought about hunting machines?
Well, they don't get that looking
dependents wrong.
You Somehow they wrong assault.
They were still fever.
So they have to die that way too.
So you hunt them down to help others?
No, no.
For school.
I can't wait for wars.
Life's too short.
And the thrill of death to shut.
If you kill a tribes me, I'll be Richard Hunt of war.
They complain if you waste the meat.
But bandits, they're vicious.
They always put up a fight.
And no one cares if you kill them.
Hi.
Guess you're doing the right thing for the wrong reason.
I'm doing what I will.
Anyone could be.
Is that we're done here?
Here?
I'm afraid, Sale, but we live in a world of ruins.
Bandits have drawn to them like infection.
Doable?
He wouldn't infection.
Said,
I'm sure.
Only looking.
Maybe if it can't be helped if we pass each other, die around the clock.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Yeah.
You
okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
This
It's just sure.
Yeah,
well, we will come up.
I think that's just okay.
prosperous,
right?
Yeah.
Uh huh.
I think.
All right,
sound.
What is in the same way,
right?
Yeah.
And
which
Yeah.
Thank you.
Yeah,
it's been
Yeah, right.
Mhm.
Yeah,
this is
Come on.
Yeah,
Well,
can't hit him.
Yeah.
Oh,
good.
Yeah.
Always this
mhm need.
Yes.
Yeah,
yeah.
No,
no.
Yeah,
yeah.
Mhm.
Why about
okay?
Yeah.
Guests coming for you.
Quit.
Okay, let's just tell.
Mhm.
Yeah,
Thanks.
Mhm.
Ross will live on and all mothers memory seeker.
And in mine.
Okay.
Talking
with her second village that Maria spoke off in shambles.
Come on.
Mhm.
Just
You're scanning for me.
here they come.
Corrupted washers.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
I don't remember.
Just
Okay,
that's it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Mhm.
And what I can to cause this Valley of corruption.
Time to see if the card affords Will let me pass over the mountains.
All personnel currently assigned to company E, Fifth Battalion, third civilian Guard Brigade, Aurora Zone one.
Report to verdict.
Carrier Bay on exit.
0, 500 hours and board assigned vert departure at 05 30 hours to arrive in bear Mozambican.
Approximately 0 100 hours.
Local time.
Lodging assignments and duty schedules to be received upon landing and intake.
Three assists F A D and personnel in Mozambican civilian battalions in a construction of defensive obstacles along the Channel Coast and be ballistic perimeter shielding around the airport.
Oh, Internazionale Deborah four.
Upon completion of construction duties, participate in combat and base defense training operations in anticipation of enemy contact.
Five.
As always, comport yourself.
So is to be a credit to your unit, your country goals of Operation Enduring Victory and yourself.
Special orders end
yeah.